

CONTACT

+84 354 123 027

HCMC, An Khanh Ward, Mai Chi Tho BLV No 17

SKILLS

- Fast Learner
- · Detail Orientated
- Analytical
- Report Writing and Presentation
- · Market Research
- Time Management

LANGUAGES

- Vietnamese (Excellent)
- English (Good)
- Mandarin (Good)

REFERENCE

Will Nhan

SPG Land Vietnam Deputy CEO

Phone: +84 90 918 2712

Email: will.nhan@spgland.com.vn

HUÝNH NHÃ ĐOAN

STRATEGIC PLANNING MANAGER



PROFILE

Responsible and detail-oriented strategic planning manager with over 4 years of experience in the real estate industry. I am energetic, a fast learner, and capable of effectively communicating with all levels of management to achieve bottom-line results. I am confident in my abilities and committed to delivering sustainable value while helping companies achieve long-term development goals.



WORK EXPERIENCE

SPG Land Vietnam

2020 - 2024

Strategic Planning Manager

Responsible for assisting and executing (research and collect data, consolidate, verify information, create presentation...) in these following assignment

- Product Strategy: Product Mix, Facilities/Amenities, Other Key Selling Points
- Sales Strategy: Price Model, Phasing Strategy, Channels Strategy
- Reporting: Produce market research report (weekly, monthly, quarterly),
 Sales and Marketing report, or any specific reports that be assigned by the management
- Others: CRM system, Sales kits preparation, assist Marketing Department in some special report and presentation, manage sales budget

Alpha King Real Estate Development

2019 - 2020

Strategic Planning Executive

Responsible for assisting (research and collect data, consolidate, verify information, create presentation..) in these following assignment

 Reporting: Produce market research report (weekly, monthly, quarterly),
 Sales and Marketing report, or any specific reports that be assigned by the management

New City Real Estate Company

2017 - 2019

Accountant

- Financial Record Keeping: Maintain accurate and up-to-date financial records, including ledgers, journals, and other accounting documentation.
- Accounts Payable & Receivable: Oversee the processing of invoices, payments, and receipts, ensuring proper cash flow management.



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Accounting

Banking University of Ho Chi Minh City

GPA: 7.37 / 10

2013 - 2017